Luis Alberto Ceren

Software Developer

Medellín, Colombia | +57 314 510 3005 | https://github.com/lcerenc661

Software developer with experience in product design and project management. 1+ work experience on the development of frontend and backend solutions, integrating cloud services with CI/CD practices. I am characterized by a proactive mindset and a commitment to continuous improvement, which drives me to constantly study and learn new technologies and concepts.

Professional Experience

FullStack Developer - Aim Edge Apps

April 2024 - Present

- Develop and mantain of web and mobile applications for our clients using technologies such as React, Next.js, Nest.js, Express.js, Flutter, AWS services, and MySQL.
- Participate in the estimation and design of new projects.
- Propose and promote best practices to improve our code quality, project architercture, and development processes.
- Conduct to research on new technologies and create proof of concepts to evaluate their potential for integration into ongoing projects.

Bilingual Analyst - Nation Wide Legal

October 2023 - April 2024

 Generated subpoenas for law firms located in California (USA), understanding the different requirements and legislation for serving them.

Product Development Engineer - AKT Motos

February 2021 - December 2022

- Coordinated the design, development, and production of plastic subproducts through direct interaction with suppliers and the assembly line.
- Designed graphic pieces for motorcycles and other needs of the area.

Skills

Technical

Python TypeScript JavaScript
Dart (Flutter) AWS SQL React
Nest Next.js Linux Docker

Languages

Spanish: NativeEnglish: Fluent (C1)

Education

Software Developer -Bootcamps / Courses January 2022 - Present

Specialization in Project Management - EAFIT

Graduation date: December 2021

Product Design Engineering - *EAFIT*

Graduation date: June 2020

References

Mauricio Guzmán

Global Innovation Manager - LLYC Mobile: +57 321 8823 946

Juan Camilo Echeverrí

Full Stack Developer - Wompi Mobile: +57 316 2469 782

Alejandro Ceren

Data Quality Lead - Accenture Mobile: +57 313 6031 487